<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Cities: Skylines II Unofficial Maps Wiki Blog</title>
        <link>https://shankscs2.github.io/cs2-maps-wiki/blog</link>
        <description>Cities: Skylines II Unofficial Maps Wiki Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:18:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why a wiki]]></title>
            <link>https://shankscs2.github.io/cs2-maps-wiki/blog/why-a-wiki</link>
            <guid>https://shankscs2.github.io/cs2-maps-wiki/blog/why-a-wiki</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We wanted to create this wiki to share the tips, tricks, and workflows we have developed through Cities Skylines II. Outside of a few points in the official wiki, Cities: Skylines I map making information was difficult to find, and applying general QGIS methods to our specific needs required lots of trial and error.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We wanted to create this wiki to share the tips, tricks, and workflows we have developed through Cities: Skylines I and now into Cities: Skylines II. Outside of a few points in the official wiki, Cities: Skylines I map making information was difficult to find, and applying general QGIS methods to our specific needs required lots of trial and error.</p>
<p>We hope that this wiki will be a consolidated resource for information about map making that compliments official information made available by Colossal Order and how to apply QGIS/GIS methods towards the specific goal of creating maps for Cities: Skylines II.</p>
<p>Thanks for visting, we hope you've found this site helpful!</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>